{
  "category": "link",
  "sections": [
    {
      "title": "Music",
      "chats": [
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "- [Obscura Liturgia - Occult Dark Ambient Music - Dark Monastic Chantings - Dark Gregorian Chants](https://youtu.be/68tmj9SPfhI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:44:59.352Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "- [M A N T R A - 432Hz Healing Soundscape - Tibetan Music For Sleep & Meditation](https://youtu.be/jHMwRkLzRzA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:47:00.704Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[DUNE | Walking through the Arrakis Desert | Dune Ambient Music | Meditation, Concentration & Work](https://youtu.be/LF5hz4XzzM4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:47:51.165Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "- [4K Forest Birdsong 2 - Birds Sing in the Woods - No Loop Realtime Birdsong - Relaxing Nature Video](https://youtu.be/XxP8kxUn5bc)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:48:29.099Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "- [Forest Waterfall Nature Sounds - 1 Hour Relaxing Birds Chirping - River Meditation Sleeping Sound](https://youtu.be/iCk16sC3dP0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:49:17.874Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/narFtb5tdTQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/JNd3qk9-HkE)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/sUNeDMNTaI0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/IvUU8joBb1Q)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/POMrW2uwDKY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/b7k0a5hYnSI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/mraLsg-G4wA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/u9Dg-g7t2l4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/MF4CapjHMkI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/cE6wxDqdOV0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/1ksjdlA4i9A)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/M6JT1A-G7OE)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/Ap5gi-I6bfI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/h-PfBxoMq_4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/LuAhzB9m4e4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/McnMsFwZlvA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/qMxX-QOV9tI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/YcXMhwF4EtQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/ggSzc9NyOhc)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/-x6N1qaVWho)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/6xTQxSkTXww)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/yCGFfz7LfDQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/9ckv6-yhnIY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/F0Pvtpwrn0A)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/p3FsbF_Aito)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/Kpq6Xu1_rB8)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/UJtB55MaoD0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/SDFdzLJBH7g)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://www.youtube.com/live/mUBqNRvsSQo)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/fHI8X4OXluQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/0tV62d09ukg)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/oGFr_NcKyfo)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/2IU7zaot30s)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/tu4HfcmMn1E)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/0RZd4Vil4VA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/LUO5qhpD2pA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/F-qE9BNvM50)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://www.youtube.com/live/a_dSl2DuqSA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/MYPVQccHhAQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/ZxrOb4Nc-oI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/I_heJ4v50Kc)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/j440-D5JhjI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/QcfIroNI3NU)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/4wEnizVOcxU)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/-MJi7T4lX80)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/VQOU1DpPDHA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/0C-lPh-V0w0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/Kt-tLuszKBA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/dwY7w0k3j2Y)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/HGl75kurxok)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/9ou1pl0XNRs)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/_ty8iK6q1gE)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/Xy6cDofZdiI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/ucqbkJVzurI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/VwLoi1OdrQs)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/oRdxUFDoQe0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/eKFTSSKCzWA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/wIMSU8otS-g)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/_SpbEmeIFj0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/i4_KiNGCEe8)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/XbcnQCHpdmE)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/YEGnOjNXMSU)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/nfbNTcL9xw0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/kIQS15N5qYQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/pTKs80LW9P4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/YlUKcNNmywk)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/1w7OgIMMRc4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/o1tj2zJ2Wvg)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/rY0WxgSXdEE)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/fJ9rUzIMcZQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/WUOtCLOXgm8)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/reGlno9aUpw)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/L3wKzyIN1yk)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/aUpmd4nm7YM)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/LXvG0SMP7tw)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/uu7j_xljCRY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/RSJbYWPEaxw)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/M6mU0wMEmbQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/6FuItxLckvA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/4ggVYsZoZiA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/ZcJxWOs64OI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/YuBeBjqKSGQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/mVUpKIFHqZk)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/Z2yNwTeSdo0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/V-znVcEJtkk)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://www.youtube.com/live/by4rdGi4hXc)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/lc0F9CKUYmI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/30b7_S0paCQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/QK2mtWjtyDU)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/HBYjbtQyJfY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/GXFSK0ogeg4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/EJC-_j3SnXk)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/AP_CSQgBPpQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/KJ_HHRJf0xg)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/CahOLfYxiq0)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/9osre3R0LvA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/xQOVm6cj7QY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/J2iBX_wGbkU)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://www.youtube.com/live/zuCRSwWssVk)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/k0B-palOEK8)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/lWNOLqs1IPQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/M5QY2_8704o)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/e1xkb9y34YA)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/ffxKSjUwKdU)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/r_XrdBIBMZs)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/CwED4C5FJuo)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/Lv8VKCz3Cdg)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/hn3wJ1_1Zsg)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/HrxX9TBj2zY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/HrxX9TBj2zY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/HrxX9TBj2zY)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/k3fz6CC45ok)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/qVTVB0Y3CA4)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/8Bo7TVZAwTw)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/-wBkKED42oo)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/ECYLHiXvrBQ)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/GOPrG1QH_2U)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        },
        {
          "indexTitle": "",
          "question": "",
          "answer": "[t](https://youtu.be/13W1J9EwqDI)",
          "dateTime": "2024-05-03T17:05:13.520Z"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}